trendybharat.com 2017-06-06

# Buy Privacy Policy | TrendyBharat Online India| TrendyBharat.com

**_INFORMATION SECURITY IS THE IMMUNE SYSTEM IN THE BODY OF BUSINESS_**

We regard our members'/customers' privacy as one of our most important values. As you may be concerned about what we do with your personal data or information, we want you to know how we protect our member information as we service your account. We understand that for you to take full advantage of TrendyBharat's services, we must ensure that your privacy is secure. We believe this policy should give you confidence whenever you use our services.

TrendyBharat recognizes the importance of privacy as well as the importance of maintaining the confidentiality of personal information of our customers, registered members and users, and have established this privacy policy as a result.

**OUR PRIVACY POLICY IS SUBJECT TO CHANGE AT ANY POINT OF TIME WITHOUT NOTICE. TO MAKE SURE YOU ARE AWARE OF ANY CHANGES, PLEASE REVIEW THIS POLICY AND THE ‘TERMS OF USE’ POLICY PERIODICALLY.**

**COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

In the course of registering for and availing various services we provide from time to time through our website (Website, telephone search, SMS and WAP) or any other Media medium in which TrendyBharat may provide services you may be required to disclose your name, residence address, email address, telephone number and similar Personal Information.

The Personal Information is used for two general purposes: to process your order, and to provide you with the best possible services. Unless otherwise stated explicitly, this Policy applies to Personal Information as disclosed on any of the Media.

In furtherance of the confidentiality with which we treat Personal Information we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We use data collection devices such as " **cookies** " on certain pages of the Site to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. 

**"Cookies"** are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Site and you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently during a session.

Additionally, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the Site that are placed by third parties. For example, if you view a web page created by a user, there may be a "cookie" placed within that web page. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Website, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

You acknowledge that apart from Your Personal Information, if You upload any content on the Website, such content may contain information including Personal Information and the same may be available to the other users of the Website. TrendyBharat will not be liable for the disclosure and dissemination of such Personal Information to third parties. 

TrendyBharat may disclose aggregated information about the use of the Website, but it will never contain Personal Information. TrendyBharat does not disclose Personal Information to third parties in the normal course of operations. However, in situations when TrendyBharat is legally obligated to disclose information to the government or other third parties, TrendyBharat will do so.

TrendyBharatimplements standard measures to protect against unauthorized access to and unlawful interception of Personal Information. However, no internet site can fully eliminate security risks.

**SHARED PERSONAL INFORMATION**

You are required to submit Your information at the time of making an online purchase on the Website. TrendyBharat uses an online payment gateway that is operated by a third party and the information that You share with TrendyBharat is transferred and shared with such third party payment gateway operator. The said operator may also have access to Your online purchase history/details that You make from the Website.

Extremely sensitive information like Your credit-card details are transacted upon secure sites of approved payment gateways which are digitally under encryption, thereby providing the highest possible degree of care as per current technology. You are advised, however, that internet technology is not 100% safe and You should exercise discretion on using the same.

**THIRD PARTIES WEBSITE**

The Website provides third-party advertisements and links to other websites. TrendyBharat does not provide any Personal Information to these third-party websites or advertisers.

In no instance is your personal information bought, traded, or sold to any other party, including market research or telemarketing corporations, for commercial purposes. We do not give out your phone number, credit card information, or screen names to anyone. The websites you might visit while connected to TrendyBharat. website may have their own privacy policies or no policy at all. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any websites you visit before providing them with any of your personal information

These third-party websites and advertisers may use technology to send the advertisements that appear on the Website directly to Your browser. In such cases, the third party websites or advertisers automatically receive Your IP address. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize advertising content. TrendyBharat does not have access to or control over cookies or other features that such third party websites and advertisers may use, and the information practices of these third-party websites and advertisers are not covered by this Policy. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices.

**MINORS**

The Sites and their contents are not targeted to minors (those under the age of 18) and we do not intend to sell any of our products or services to minors. However, we have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access our Site. If a minor has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information.

**SECURITY**

We have in place appropriate technical and security measures to prevent unauthorized access to or accidental loss of or destruction or damage to your information. When we collect data through the Site, we collect your personal details on a secure server. We use firewalls on our servers. When we collect payment card details electronically, we use encryption by using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) coding. Whilst we are unable to guarantee 100% security, this makes it hard for a hacker to decrypt your details. You are strongly recommended not to send full credit or debit card details in encrypted electronic communications with us. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of your information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you. You are responsible for protecting against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer.

Notwithstanding anything contained in this Policy or elsewhere, TrendyBharat shall not be held responsible for any loss, damage or misuse of Your Personal Information, if such loss, damage or misuse is attributable to circumstances beyond one's control.

In accordance with Information Technology Act,2000 and the rules there under the name and contact  Details of Grievance Officer shall publish on website.

** ** DISCRETION

You can always choose not to provide information and in such cases, if the information required is classified as mandatory, You will not be able to avail of that part of the Services, features or content. 

You can add or update Your Personal Information on a regular basis. When You update information, TrendyBharat will keep a copy of the prior version for its records.

TrendyBharat may, if You so choose, send direct advertisement mailers to You at the address given by You. You have the option to opt-out of this direct mailer by clicking at the unsubscribed link option attached to e-mail.

Further, You can also disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Website of its manufacturer. However, as cookies allow You to take advantage of some of the Website's features, some of the Website's features and services may not function properly if Your cookies are disabled. It is therefore, recommended that You leave the cookies turned on. For instance, if You block or otherwise reject TrendyBharat's cookies, You will not be able to add items to Your shopping cart, proceed to checkout, or download any of TrendyBharat's Content or avail of TrendyBharat's services that require You to log in.

**CONSENT**

By using the Website and/ or by providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the Website in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to Your consent for sharing your information as per this privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. ****

**COPYRIGHT**

We have copyright over this Privacy Policy. Use by third parties, even by way of extract, for commercial purposes is not allowed. Infringements may be subject to legal action.

**_The Goal as a Company is to have user service that is not just the best but legendary  _**
